A Guide to the Wayne Perkins Collection, 1835-1996
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- Series IV. Photographs and Postcards, 1887-1987.
  - Subseries A. Photographs, 1887-1976.
    - C. W. Jernstrom locomotive photos (Box-folder 4-2-7)
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1155, 1947.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1159, 1956.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1207, 1953.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1209, 1958.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1210, 1956.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1212, 1956.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1213, 1958.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1214, 1957.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1216, 1955.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1219, 1958.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1221, 1957.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1222 (with 1234), 1958.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1223, 1957.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1224, 1958.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1226, 1953.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1226, 1957.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1230, 1956.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1232, 1958.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1233, 1946.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1233, 1957.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1236, 1957.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1238, 1953.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1239, 1953.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1239, 1958.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1240, 1956.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1240, 1959.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1241, 1953.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1242, 1950.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1242, 1956.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1411, 1947.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1440, 1936.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1456, 1947.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1456, 1953.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1456, 1956.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1482, 1953.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2005, 1953.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2006, 1953.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2028, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2039, 1954.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2051, 1958.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2068, 1950.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2083, 1954.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2098, 1931.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2102, 1959.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2105, 1959.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2110, 1958.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2113, 1939.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2117, 1953.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2120, 1936.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2122, 1959.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2123, 1959.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2126, 1953.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2126, 1959.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2127, 1959.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2130, 1949.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2131, 1947.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2131, 1950.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2133, 1959.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2134, 1959.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2136, 1959.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2137, 1939.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2140, 1954.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2142, 1958.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2142, 1959.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2145, 1955.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2145, 1959.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2146, 1953.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2150, 1954.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2157, 1947.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2158, 1957.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2163, 1946.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2163, 1953.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2169, 1953.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2170, 1954.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2173, 1948.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2174, 1959.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2179, 1956.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2181, 1949.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2182, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2187, 1950.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2195, 1956.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2196, 1952.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2300 (TE-1), 1954.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2300 (TE-1), 1955.
    - John Krause locomotive photos (Box-folder 4-8-10)
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 115, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 117, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 120, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 131, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 382 at West Jefferson depot, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 611 (with 106), n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 613, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2125, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2129, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2143, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2159, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2163 at Oakvale depot, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2163, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2164, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2169, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2173, n.d.
    - R. D. Patton locomotive photos (Box-folder 4-10)
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 562, 1946.
    - Harold K. Vollrath locomotive photos (Box-folder 5-1-9)
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 3, 1952.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 7, 1949.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 29, [ca. 1898].
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 29, [ca. 1900].
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 35, 1887.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 37, 1909.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 56, 1916.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 62, 1898.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 72, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 89, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 91, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 93, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 95, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 100, 1941.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 103, 1953.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 105, 1957.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 107, 1955.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 112, 1957.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 113, 1958.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 114, 1950.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 115, 1954.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 116, 1956.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 118, 1952.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 120, 1935.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 120, 1950.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 121, 1952.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 124, 1948.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 128, 1948.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 129, 1950.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 130, 1956.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 133, 1955.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 136, 1934.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 136, 1956.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 141, 1912.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 201, 1926.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 201, 1927.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 202, 1935.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 203, 1938.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 205, 1926.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 207, 1891.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 214, 1910.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 230, 1910.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 235, 1961.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 256, 1922.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 302, 1934.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 375, 1949.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 375, 1957.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 376, 1958.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 382, 1956.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 392, 1949.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 396, 1952.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 405, 1955.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 429, 1957.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 457, 1949.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 459, 1949.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 475, [1954?].
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 475, 1957.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 477, 1955.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 484, 1949.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 495, 1951.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 500, 1938.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 528, 1909.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 543, 1936.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 546, 1941.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 547, 1918.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 555, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 557, 1951.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 562, 1940.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 563, 1936.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 564, 1948.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 566, 1948.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 572, 1937.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 578, 1957.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 595, 1939.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 596, 1921.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 596, 1925.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 597, 1925.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 600, 1917.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 600, 1946.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 601, 1952.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 602, 1916.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 603, 1925.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 603, 1957.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 604, 1947.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 605, 1943.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 605, [1954?].
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 606, 1903.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 607, 1949.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 607, 1955.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 608, 1950.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 608, 1951.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 608, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 609, 1953.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 611, 1956.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 612, 1953.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 613, 1958.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 674, 1949.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 690, 1950.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 800, 1925.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 800, 1949.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 809, 1949.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 819, 1900.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 825, 1949.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 825, 1952.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 884, 1936.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 885, [1954?].
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 902, 1953.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 914, 1940.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 929, [1934?].
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 940, 1947.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 944, 1940.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 953, [1934?].
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 954, 1936.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 954, 1948.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 956, 1948.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 990, 1911.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 999, 1910.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 999, 1914.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1000, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1012, 1936.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1027, 1921.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1060, 1938.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1060, 1938.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1100, 1940.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1100, 1949.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1103, 1947.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1112, 1951.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1117, 1953.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1119, 1941.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1122, 1950.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1128, 1953.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1130, 1916.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1131, 1952.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1138, 1911.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1138, 1949.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1141, 1937.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1147, 1940.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1148, 1952.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1150, 1953.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1153, 1947.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1154, 1941.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1155, 1948.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1159, 1956.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1201, 1955.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1205, 1949.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1206, 1953.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1207, 1959.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1209, 1958.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1211, 1953.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1212, 1958.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1214, 1957.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1215, 1953.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1216, 1956.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1217, 1955.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1219, 1953.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1219, 1955.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1225, 1957.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1232, 1949.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1235, 1958.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1236, [1954].
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1238, 1953.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1319, 1937.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1321, 1938.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1323, 1936.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1355, 1949.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1362, 1957.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1364, 1946.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1374, 1948.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1403, 1949.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1415, 1936.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1420, 1953.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1429, 1953.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1442, 1950.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1442, 1956.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1476, 1953.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1478, 1936.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1483, 1956.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1700, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1701, 1938.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1716, 1949.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1717, 1947.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2003, 1948.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2009, 1956.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2010, 1949.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2017, 1941.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2023, 1957.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2028, 1955.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2038, 1957.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2040, [1954?].
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2043, 1956.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2047, 1953.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2056, 1949.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2057, 1957.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2068, 1942.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2081, 1948.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2101, 1958.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2110, 1953.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2112, [1954?].
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2114, 1950.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2120, [1941?].
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2125, 1955.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2126, 1959.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2134, 1953.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2135, 1941.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2136, [1954?].
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2140, 1952.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2141, 1941.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2142, 1953.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2142, 1958.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2143, 1955.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2147, 1960.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2153, 1957.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2174, 1957.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2177, 1959.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2179, [1954?].
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2193, 1955.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2200, 1953.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2200, 1957.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2300, [1954?].
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2508, 1940.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2511, 1930.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2512, 1915.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway unidentified locomotive, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway caboose 518423, 1949.
    - Charles E. Winters locomotive photos (Box-folder 5-9)
      - Southern Railway 1554, 1934.
    - Uncredited locomotive and train photos (Box-folder 6-1-8)
      - Allegany Central Railroad, n.d.
      - Baltimore & Ohio Railroad 3501, 1966.
      - Baltimore & Ohio Railroad 5320, 1950.
      - Buckeye Coal & Coke Company steam locomotive, 1940.
      - Butte, Anaconda and Pacific Railway 51, n.d.
      - Camino Placerville & Lake Tahoe 2, 1959.
      - Canadian Pacific Railway 2317, 1966.
      - Cass Scenic Railroad, n.d.
      - Grand Trunk Western Railroad 6039 (at Steamtown National Historic Site), 1966.
      - Illinois Central Railroad 602, 1964.
      - Illinois Central Railroad 2409, n.d.
      - Kanawha, Glen Jean & Eastern Railway, 1913, n.d.
      - New Hope & Ivyland Railroad 1533, 1966.
      - New York Central Railroad 6033, 1965.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 19, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 89, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 114, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 131, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 220, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 382 (at Green Cove Station), n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 477, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 602, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 603, 1941.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 603, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 605, 1925.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 605, 1943.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 605 (with Powhatan Arrow), 1947.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 607 (with Powhatan Arrow), 1950.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 608, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 609 (with Powhatan Arrow), 1949.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 611, ca. 1975.
        [7 items]
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 613, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 675, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1200, 1936.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1200, 1939.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1206, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1242, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1462, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1641 (accident), n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1776, ca. 1976.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2058, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2129, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2135, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2138, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2142, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2163, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway unidentified locomotive with Powhatan Arrow, 1949.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway unidentified locomotives with freight trains, n.d.
      - Pennsylvania Railroad 1641, 1941.
      - Pennsylvania Railroad 4411, 1966.
      - Pennsylvania Railroad 4848, n.d.
      - Pennsylvania Railroad 4894, 1967.
      - Pennsylvania Railroad 4903, n.d.
      - Pennsylvania Railroad 4931, 1965.
      - Pennsylvania Railroad 5879, n.d.
      - Pennsylvania Railroad 7623, 1966.
      - Pennsylvania Railroad MU 251, 1965.
      - Pennsylvania Railroad MU 269, 1964.
      - Pennsylvania Railroad electric multiple-unit cars, 1963-1967.
      - Reading Railroad 2018, 1940.
      - St. John's Railway 7, 1966.
      - Santa Fe Railway 16, 1964.
      - Southern Pacific 1360, 1964.
      - Southern Railway (unidentified), n.d.
      - Union Pacific Railroad 199B, 1964.
      - Union Pacific Railroad 405, 1964.
      - Union Pacific Railroad 1850, 1964.
      - Virginia Blue Ridge Railway 9, n.d.
      - White Oak Railway 199, n.d.
      - Unidentified locomotives, n.d.
        [18 items]
    - Other rolling stock photos (Box-folder 6-9)
      - Geary Street Cable Road cable car (San Francisco), ca. 1890.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway cabooses, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway passenger cars, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway train wreck on trestle, ca. 1930.
      - Wrecking crew recovering train wreck in small town, [1960s?].
      - Wrecking train at work, n.d.
      - Engines, cars and wrecking train at Bluefield, West Virginia train yard, [1980s?].
        [15 items]
    - Railroad-related and general scenery, A-Z (Box-folder 7-1)
      - Cambria (Christiansburg), Virginia railroad crossing and freight depot 1932.
      - Glen Jean [West Virginia] saloon interior, n.d.
      - Grayson train station and Heusel/Ribble family group, [1890s?].
      - Ivanhoe train station, n.d.
      - Mill Creek Coal & Coke Company - Elkhorn tipple in Barlow Hollow [Maybeury, West Virginia], n.d.
      - Phoenix Camp [West Virginia] on Ohio Extension, Norfolk & Western Railway, 1892.
      - Royal Coal Company tipple, 1908.
      - Thurmond, West Virginia business section n.d.
      - Zanesville, Ohio dog mines, n.d.
    - Railroad-related and general scenery, unidentified (Box-folder 7-2)
      [3 folders]
      - Unidentified home, n.d.
      - Unidentified train yard [probably Roanoke, Virginia], n.d.
      - Train tracks in warehouse district of unidentified town, n.d.
      - Unidentified small abandoned train station, n.d.
      - "Gag" photo of worker crushed by railroad cars, n.d.
      - Unidentified train station [probably Rural Retreat, Virginia] [ca. 1975].
        [12 items]
      - Unidentified train station, n.d.
      - Scenes and people in West Virginia / Southwest Virginia, [ca. 1925].
        [14 items; negatives only]
      - Bendix-Feragen automobile frame-straightening equipment in unidentified shop, [1935?].
        [24 items]
      - Charles A. Lindbergh with mother and "Spirit of St. Louis," n.d.
        [includes auto-pen reproduced signature]
  - Subseries B. Postcards, [1906?]-1987.
    - Locomotives and trains (Box-folder 7-3-5)
      - Amtrak, n.d.
      - California Western Railroad 45, n.d.
      - Cass Scenic Railroad, n.d.
      - Cincinnati, Hamilton and Dayton Railroad depot (Glendale, Ohio), 1911.
      - Hocking Valley Scenic Railway, n.d.
      - Milwaukee Road 218, [1956?].
      - Milwaukee Road 265, 1957.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 121, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 244, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 375, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 382, 1957.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 600 (with Tennessean passenger train), n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 601 (with passenger train), 1952.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 603, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 610, 1954.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 611 (large format), 1957.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 611, 1982.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 611, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1206, 1959.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1218, 1987.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 1776, 1974, n.d.
        [3 items, including 1 large format]
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2141 (near Pembroke, Virginia), n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 2171, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 8521 1971.
      - "Historic Norfolk & Western Railway Post Card Set" (published by Mary Jayne's Railroad Specialties)
        - Norfolk & Western Railway 95, 1883.
        - Norfolk & Western Railway 126, 1939.
        - Norfolk & Western Railway 207, n.d.
        - Norfolk & Western Railway 244, 1953.
        - Norfolk & Western Railway 575, 1912.
        - Norfolk & Western Railway 575, 1944.
        - Norfolk & Western Railway 1399, 1929.
        - Norfolk & Western Railway 2137, 1946.
        - Norfolk & Western Railway 2300, 1955.
        - Norfolk & Western Railway 2505 (electric), 1929.
        - Virginian Railway 234 (electric), 1960.
        - Virginian Railway 737, 1949.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 600, 1203 and 2123, 1945.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway 600, 1203 and 2123, n.d.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway Memphis Special passenger train, 1911-1916.
      - Norfolk & Western Railway Powhatan Arrow tavern-lounge-observation car, n.d.
      - Santa Fe 16C, 1967.
      - Santa Fe 60, 1967.
      - Southern Pacific unidentified locomotive, 1947.
      - Southern Railway 630, 1968.
      - Richmond, Fredericksburg & Potomac 617, [1958?].
      - Virginian Railway 138, 1957.
      - Virginian Railway 212, 1957.
      - Virginian Railway 700, n.d.
      - Unidentified, [1915?].
      - Wild River Route (featuring Reading Railroad 2102), [1971?].
    - Railroad-related scenery (Box-folder 7-6)
      - Bedford, Virginia: Norfolk & Western Railway passenger station, 1908.
      - Crystal, West Virginia, n.d.
      - Glendale, Ohio: Cincinnati, Hamilton & Dayton Railway depot, 1911.
      - Harrisburg, Pennsylvania: "scene along the main line near Rockville Bridge," n.d.
      - Mobile, Alabama: new terminal station, 1917.